wallstreetinsanity.com 2017-06-30

# Privacy Policy | Wall Street Insanity

Privacy Policy:  
WallStreetInsanity.com takes your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes what information we collect and how we use it.

Website Visitors:  
Like most web sites WallStreetInsanity.com collects information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as but not limited to, the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. 

WallStreetInsanity.com may also collect and store information that you provide such as your email address when you sign up for the WallStreetInsanity.com newsletter. 

WallStreetInsanity.com purpose in collecting this information includes the following general purposes: to personalize the content you see, fulfill your requests, contact you, and to improve our services. 

Cookies:  
We may place a cookie on your personal computer. A cookie is a small computer file that our computer sends to your computer and that your computer sends back to us each time you make a request from our site. Cookies help us recognize you when you visit our site again. We use cookies on our site to collect session data for several purposes to personalize and improve your individual viewing experiences on our site. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. However, you can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or prompt you before accepting a cookie from the sites you visit. 

Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.

Email Policy:  
WallStreetInsanity.com collects email and other personal Contact Data at times. We may use Contact Data to send you information about our company or our products or services, to improve our site, contact you when necessary, or send you promotional material from our partners. We may use your Demographic Data to customize and tailor your experience on the Web Site; displaying content that we think you might be interested in and according to your preferences.

We may also use Contact Data for lead generation purpose by sending you information about products or services, or promotional material of other third party companies.

Information Sharing:  
WallStreetInsanity.com does not share information about you with third parties or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:  
• We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;  
• We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of WallStreetInsanity.com’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.  
• We transfer information about you if WallStreetInsanity.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, WallStreetInsanity.com will try to notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Changes to Privacy Policy:  
WallStreetInsanity.com may update this policy at any time without notice. Please check back for any changes.
